In which country should
В какой стране должен отойти
Crimea go to Russia, in fact, with the consent of
Крым фактически России по согласию
Ukraine? Uh-huh, I understand, that is, you are not
Украины Угу понял то есть вы так не вы
so against it, but Ukraine must
так против во то Украина должна
agree that, that is, you are against war,
согласиться что то есть вы против войны
but Ukraine must agree to the
но Украина должна согласиться на ээ
demands of the aggressor
требования агрессора
Yes, hello, dear
Да здравствуйте уважаемый
Hello, Can I ask the
Здравствуйте Можете вот интересуюсь у
Russians about  repression of patriotic
русских про репрессии патриотических
bloggers Why in Russia Strelko,
блогеров Почему в России стрелко
you know, in my opinion he went too far,
вы знаете по-моему палку перегнул
for example
например
Well, what needs to be
Ну тем что надо
done, what did he say that he went too far,
делать что он такое сказал что перегнул
that he was
палку что его
imprisoned Well, he turned healthy constructive
посадили Ну здоровую конструктивную
criticism into criticism,
критику превратил в критиканство
for example, for what phrase he was
например за какую фразу его
beaten, lie exactly the phrase, but I saw that
подили лежи именно фразу но я видел что
the guy is catching up And in Russia you can
парень нагоняет А в России можно за
go to prison for criticizing,
критиканство в тюрьму попасть
but for provocations you can, but what kind of
так за провокации можно а что он за
provocation
провокацию
did he do? I’m not particularly familiar with the rifleman. I
сделал Я не особо знаком со стрелковым Я
know him as a brave man who ran in with
знаю его как храброго человека который с
fifty
пятидесятью
comrades, it’s just now
соратниками забежал просто сейчас
it turns out that all these Who were in the Russian spring
получается всех этих Кто в русской весне
or were killed  or they imprisoned this [ __ ], it
был или убили или посадили это фигня
turns out the revolution devours its
получается револю пожирает своих
creators, like it ate them up, but like I do
создателей как то она их сожрала да типа
n’t know, I’m not very good at this Well, Girkin
не знаю я не особо в этом Ну а гиркин
Strelkov somehow you know how when
стрелков как-то знаете как когда
healthy criticism we support We
здоровая критика мы поддерживаем Нам
like Well, when criticism and
нравится Ну когда критиканство и
populism are already superfluous I I don’t  I completely
популизм это уже лишние я я не совсем
understand how it is under your
понимаю как там по вашему
legislation Because I don’t know, it’s
законодательству Потому что я не знаю
just that Prigozhin who made a military
просто Пригожин который сделал военный
mutiny captured Rostov and then shot down
мятеж захватил Ростов потом сбил там
about eight or how many of these
что-то восемь или сколько этих
aircraft are yours Yes from the Pilot
летательных аппаратов ваши Да с Лётчика
Yes he is free and the shooters for
Да он на свободе а стрелков за то что
writing something in  Telegram
что-то писал в Telegram
Yurgi is also a mystery for me. You know, I
юрги для меня это тоже загадка Знаете
don’t understand that the Azov people were
мне непонятны то что азовцев выпустили
probably also released by our guys. They
наверное тоже наши ребята Под прикрытием
were undercover so that suddenly it turns out later that
были так что вдруг потом выяснится что
these are our Scouts. Otherwise, I don’t understand
это наши Разведчики Иначе я не понимаю
why they were released, I’ll say they were exchanged for
почему их выпустили я скажу обменяли на
Medvedchuk’s godfather because for Ukraine
кума медведчука потому что для Украины
for Russia Medvedchuk  more important than some
для России Медведчук важнее чем какие-то
Russian soldiers, that’s why they exchanged it for
русские солдатики поэтому обменяли на
Medvedchuk. Well, enlighten me, why for
медведчука Ну просветите зачем на
Medvedchuk? I see you are a very knowledgeable
Медведчук Я вижу вы очень знающий
person. He’s Putin’s godfather; all these are
человек Он кум Путина всё это
family ties; his everything; and Yanukovych;
родственные связи свой всё а Янукович А
why did we
зачем мы его зачем мы Януковича к себе
take him?
забрали А для того чтобы да Для того
So that he doesn’t start talking here Yes, so that he
чтобы он тут не начал говорить Да чтоб
starts telling me because if our
мне начал говорить потому что если наши
organs took him Yes, he would have so many
его органы взяли Да он бы столько всего
interesting things He told you, and
интересного Рассказал так вот
you know what else is cool Navalny
а знаете что ещё прикольно Навальный
fit in with Strelkov You heard this
вписался за Стрелкова Вы слышали этот
joke Well, I don’t know, you heard Well, Navalny
прикол Ну не знаю слышали Ну Навальный
said that Strelkov is needed  to judge for
сказал что Стрелкова надо судить за
military actions and
военные действия а
for the type of entry in the telegram you can’t judge
за типа записи в телеграме нельзя судить
that he recognizes Strelkovo as a
что он признаёт стрелково
political prisoner in general Laughing Strelkovo is a
политзаключённым вообще ржака стрелково
patriot They threw Navalny into prison and
патриота Кинули в тюрьму Навальный и
Nagen writes in for him what’s going on there
наген за него вписывает что у вас там
I’m shocked really
происходит Я в шоке реально
what’s
что
happening is not happening I went too far with the
происходит не происходит я переборщил
guy with
парень с
criticism I’m just  I can’t understand, well, that
критикой Я просто не могу понять ну то
is, in America, someone criticizes him, they
есть в Америке ти кто-то критикует его
took him to jail, like,
взяли посадили типа ну
damn, and Navalny fits in behind the arrow. I
блин и Навальный вписывается за стрел У
just have another If you know what the
меня просто ещё Если знаете какая самая
biggest laugh
большая ржака
will be if this happens, I don’t know, I’ll
будет если такой будет я не знаю я
take some coffee like that, I’ll sit down
короче возьму такой кофеёк сяду короче
anyway, Wow  it’s shorter It’s just that the directing
таки Вау это короче Просто режиссура
is awesome
офигенная
Well, I don’t know. I think he’s still
Ну не знаю Мне кажется он до сих пор
our active hero of the shooters. Yes, but
действующий наш герой стрелков Да но
something is working in
что-то действует в
prison. Well, according to the secret assignments there, then he was
тюрьме Ну по заданию тайные задания там
secretly given the task of serving
тос там ему дали тайно задание посидеть
in
в
prison for these
тюрме этих
for sex and a cunning move, you never know what  we will be
за пол и хитрый ход мало ли чем нас
surprised later under Stalin, there were so many agents, and everyone was in
потом удивят при Сталине столько агентов
prison, but they didn’t
было да сидели все кто кто кого не
shoot anyone. Yes, some agents were
расстреляли Да одних агентов
shot, while others went on special assignments to
расстреливали А другие на спецзадание в
concentration camps. Yes, to watch other
концлагеря шли Да наблюдать за другими
agents. Yes, in general, everyone was agents and
агентами Да в общем все были агентами и
it is not clear who the heroes were. Yes, it’s cool,
непонятно кто там герои Да прикольно
Navalny also knows your Agent
Навальный тоже ваш Агент
Wait, well, maybe this is
зна Подождите ну это может
a multi-step move, I wouldn’t
многоходовочка
like it
такая не не хотелось бы вот это
myself Well, I wouldn’t want it, you know, well,
сам Ну не хотелось бы знаете да ну
look at this on purpose, Putin made
смотрите это специально вот Путин сделал
agents on purpose Yes, among the liberals there is a
специально агентов Да среди либералов
patriot there, Navalny is among the
среди там патриота вот Навальный среди
liberals Agent so
либералов Агент
that the followers go and we see the
у чтобы последователи пошли а мы увидели
followers also go to prison  Yes, they took him
последователи тоже в тюрьму Да его взяли
to prison, like everyone who married him. At the
типа в тюрьму все кто вышел за него На
rally
митинг
[music]
[музыка]
he may not be sitting in
он может не сидит в
a cell, he has a three-star number, in short,
камере у него там трёхзвёздочные короче
there’s a number, yes, like there’s a swimming pool there, there’s a
там номерочек да типа там бассейни есть
personal one. Anything can
там личный ещё всякий Всякое может
happen. Well, I don’t know, I don’t like him as an Agent.
быть Ну не знаю мне как Агент он не
to be honest, what kind of
нравится честно говоря какая у него
agents does he have, maybe it’s somehow not very
агентура может быть такой как-то не
good and this Prigozhin is an agent or he’s
очень а этот Пригожин он агент или он
just a fool Well, he went to Prigozhin
просто дурак Ну что он пошёл на Пригожин
You know, well, from our cynical conversation with you
Знаете ну из нашего с вами циничного
And now I’ll say seriously
такого разговора А сейчас серьёзно скажу
Prigozhin I don’t understand why he’s here,
Пригожин Я не понимаю зачем он вот
look  I find it unpleasant that such a
смотрите я мне неприятно что вот такая
structure as Wagner represents my
структура как Вагнер представляет моё
state. Well, I understand. I give it its due.
государство Ну я понимаю Я отдаю должное
As a man there as a businessman, that is,
Как мужчине там как коммерсанту то есть
how to create, well, these people should be guarding some wells, oil pipelines somewhere in
как создать ну эти люди должны где-то в
Africa,
Африке охранять какие-то скважины
something something Well  something like
нефтепроводы там что-то что-то Ну как-то
this Yeah, I
так
understood that is, it’s an incomprehensible
Угу понял то есть это непонятная
structure, it’s not the Russian army, it’s not
структура это не Российская армия это не
some kind of Ministry of Internal Affairs there, it’s something, well, it’s a
какие-то МВД там это что-то ну что это
commercial structure and it doesn’t represent
коммерческая структура и представляет
my homeland very well. For example, well,
мою родину не очень смот Вот например ну
Putin there’s still one fate there. Maybe it will be
Путин там ещё там один рок Может будет
there  maybe lives Who after Putin is
там может живёт Кто после Путина вот
who you see as president after
кого вы видите президентом после
Putin
Путина
who will be drawn I see I don’t know
кого кого нарисуют того я вижу я не знаю
who
а кто это
draws this too you know it would be interesting to
рисует тоже знаете было бы любопытно
know who draws this I thought that you
узнать кто это рисует Я думал что Вы
elect these rulers
избирает этих правителей
of yours Judging by your eyes I think you
своих Судя по вашим глазам Я думаю вы
do  we didn’t think that you were electing someone,
так не думали что и вы кого-то избирает
we
мы
were electing,
избираем да
yes, yes, we got up in the morning with a feeling of patriotism,
да с утра встали с чувством патриотизма
we put on a white shirt, we went to the polls,
одели белую рубашку пошли на выборы
elections,
выборы
Yes, to fulfill the Civil House, I, I even
Да исполнять Гражданский дом я я даже в
went to the polls in an embroidered shirt, and this happened
вышиванке ходил на выборы и такое было
Well, I understand, I understand why you are that yours  the
Ну я я понимаю Понимаю начем вы что ваш
left eye says that Well, somehow
левый глаз говорит о том что Ну как-то
it wasn’t quite like that, not yet Well, again
не совсем это было так не ещё Ну ещё раз
Well, what’s the point, well, you don’t go to
Ну а в чём типа ну вы не ходите на
the polls You go to the
выборы Вы ходите на
polls once, I went to the polls Yes, but that’s just one thing, and it was a
выборы один раз ходил Да а что один
matter of chance I was in the hospital  I was lying
а дело случая было я в больнице лежал
There the choice as this point was come straight
Там выбор как это пункт был зашли прямо
to you ty as a
к вам ти как
choice to go far not Well, like there’s
выбор далеко ходить не Да ну типа делать
nothing to do and left the room when I
нечего и пошёл из палаты когда я
went down to vote It turned out that I had
спустился проголосовать Выяснилось что я
already
уже
voted
проголосовал
cool Uh-huh and that you also somehow raised the
прикольно Угу и что и Вы как-то подняли
question This is why for  you
вопрос Это что почему за вас
were voted Yes, I shouted there and
проголосовали Да я кричал там то и всё
said everything called
говорил
on the United Nations Organization
призывал организацию Объединённых Наций
League of Nations the same thing In general, shouted
Лигу Наций то же самое В общем кричал
threatened I was told Calm down, here’s
грозил мне сказали Успокойтесь вот вам
another bulletin for you And it was just a mistake
ещё бюлетень А это была просто ошибка
something like that Uh-huh I understand yes How are you
как-то так Угу Понял да А как вы отно
farther from the hospital anyway  they didn’t send it, but
дальше больницы всё равно не отправили а
how do you feel about the war against
как вы относитесь к войне против
Ukraine, it’s disgustingly negative And you are
Украины отвратительно отрицательно А вы
also negative, and whose is Crimea, and how do
тоже отрицательно а Крым чей а а то как
you feel positively, and Crimea, whose
вы относитесь положительно а Крым чей
Crimea is legally Ukrainian, mentally
Крым юридически украинский ментально
Russian and in fact Russian, do you
российский и фактически российский вы
think which country should
как считаете какой стране должен отойти
Crimea go to Russia, in fact, with the consent of
Крым фактически России по согласию
Ukraine  Yeah, I understand, that is, you are not
Украины Угу понял то есть вы так не вы
so against the war, but Ukraine must
так против во то Украина должна
agree that you are against the war,
согласиться что то есть вы против войны
but Ukraine must agree to the
но Украина должна согласиться на
demands of the aggressor,
э требования агрессора да
excuse me, you disappeared for a second, the beech is
простите вы пропали на секундочку бук
against the war, but Ukraine must
против войны но Украина должна
agree to the demands of the
согласиться на требовани
aggressor. Well, did you know Crimea was  captured
агрессора Ну знаете ли Крым был захвачен
in jewelry with almost no casualties, there are almost
ювелирно почти без жертв там почти
four people for this
четыре человека за это
Applause Now And this war is incomprehensible to me,
Аплодисменты Вот теперь А эта война мне
that is, everything is done rudely without
непонятно то есть всё делается грубо без
logic without common sense
логики без здравого смыслам
after Crimea somehow Don’t you think that in
после Крыма как-то А вы не думаете что в
Crimea the Armed Forces went smoothly because Ukraine
Крыму ВС было гладко потому что Украина
wanted to solve this  peacefully so that there would
хотела решить это мирным путём для того
be no
чтобы не было
casualties if Ukraine started
жертв если бы Украина начала боевые
hostilities. Yes, this would have happened right away in Crimea.
действия Да было бы сразу такое в Крыму
Ukraine wanted the last thing. What are you
Украина последнего хотела гово Что вы
doing, let’s somehow solve this all
делаете ти давайте как-то это всё решим
normally and I
нормально и
admit everything, you know from the other side, such
всё допускаю знаете с той стороны такие
thoughts from this one from
мысли с этой
Crimea  Jeweler
с Крым Ювелир
Ott that's all the rest Of course this is
Отт вот всё остальное Конечно же это
nonsense It shouldn't be something like this
нонсенс Так не должно быть как-то так Ну
But in general this war started I think
а вообще вот эту войну начала Я считаю
both sides are equally to blame Russia and
виноваты обе стороны одинаково Росси и
Uri and America is not not America Why is there
Ури а Америка не не Америка Зачем
no America this is not something something here
Америки нет сей не что-то что-то тут
wrong again, how is Russia
неправильно ещё раз как это Россия
Ukraine Ukraine an independent
Украина Украина самостоятельное
state or is it governed by America
государство или оно управляется Америкой
Ukraine Yes,
Украина Да
its independent president, you want
самостоятельная свой президент хотите
to say that ours is happy and the president
сказать что наша рада и президент
makes a decision without orders from
принимает решение без указки из
Washington with recommendations but without
Вашингтона с рекомендациями но без
orders Holy [ __ ], you’re really the first to
указки [__] реально вы первый первый
say that Ukraine really
кто говорит что Украина реально
makes its own decisions  for this,
самостоятельно принимает решение за это
respect to you Well, there is the second part of my T
респект Ну там есть вторая часть моего Т
blame for the fact that the war broke out
вину за то что развязалась война
Explain now and not America
Объясните вот тепер а не Америка
Explain yes What is Ukraine’s fault that
Объясните да В чём виновата Украина что
Russia attacked Ukraine Well, let’s be
Россия напала на Украину А ну давайте
interesting Ukraine provoked Russia
интересно Украина спровоцировала Россию
to attack provoked That is, for
на нападение спровоцировала То есть
example, if you go  down the street and someone
например если вы идёте по улице а кто-то
decided to snatch your phone from you, are you to blame
решил отжать у вас телефон вы виноваты
because you provoked this
потому что вы спровоцировали этого
attack,
напада
yes no Dear, if I’m walking and some
да нет Уважаемые если я иду и какой-то
guy in yellow shorts waving a gilyay yells
мужик в жёлтых трусах размахивая гиляй
at me, can you hear me? Yes, now I’m yes Toda
орёт мне Слышишь ты Да сейчас я да Тода
That’s it, I just walked past.  he’s two three,
Всё я раз прошёл Мимо обошёл его два три
but this guy is somehow addicted to
но этот мужик как-то пристрастился к
this, that Well, he always plans to
этому что Ну у него в планах всегда меня
meet me, call me names, insult me, and so
встретить обозвать оскорбить так вот
somehow I had to ask Kat to
пришлось как-то так набуд Кать чтобы
say, well, because I sometimes go with the children
сказал ну потому что я бывает с детьми
or something like that Well  wait, you
иду или как-то что-то Ну подождите вы
lived in Russia, the Ukrainians lived in
себе жили в России украинцы жили в
Ukraine, and somewhere on Red
Украине да где-то к вам на Красную
Square Ukrainians came to you that Well,
Площадь приезжали украинцы что Ну не
I can’t understand where they waved at you. Where did you
могу понять где там вам махали Где вы
go? Where did they wave at you? Where did they wave at
ходили А где вам гиляй где махали А где
you?
вам гиляй махали Ну там у себя скакали
couple Well, look again, that is, we in
за паре Ну ещё раз смотри то есть мы в
Ukraine were jumping about something at home and you
Украине что-то скакали у себя дома и вы
decided to come to our home and
решили прийти к нам домой и на нас
attack us like that Yes, I’m tired of it, you know, it’s scary,
напасть так Да надоело знаете ли страшно
so look, we, as a sovereign
значит смотрите мы как суверенное
state, are doing something at home in
государство что-то у себя делаем дома в
our country  you don’t like this for some
своей стране вам это по каким-то
reason and you come and
соображениям не нравится и вы приходите
kill hundreds of thousands of people, we didn’t come
убиваете сотни тысяч людей мы не пришли
to kill. Why did you come, actually, we
убивать А что вы пришли вообще-то мы
want to agree on
хотим договориться
how and what to agree on so that we don’t
какм о чём договориться чтобы мы не
talk about the Gilyak?
скакали про гиляку
Well, as if we don’t enter into military
Да ну как бы чтобы не вступали военные
alliances, let’s say  stop stop stop then you
союзы допустим стоп стоп стоп то вы
came so that we would not enter into military
пришли чтобы мы не вступали в военные
alliances or you would come we jumped with Gilya
союзы или вы пришли бы мы прыгали с Гиля
Kami Well, apparently, and then and behind this
ками Ну судя по всему и затем и за этим
somehow you have a Russophobic attitude once again
как-то у вас русофобские настрое ещё раз
what we must agree on Let's talk
о чём мы должны договориться Давайте ещё
about what again  we must come to an agreement and
раз о чём мы должны договориться и
stop the shooting, establish
прекратить стрельбу наладить
good neighborly relations, what? Well,
добрососедские отношения что по Ну давай
look, in order to stop
смотрите для того чтобы прекратить
the shooting, you need to leave Ukraine
стрельбу нужно чтобы вы ушли из Украины
and the shooting will stop. It’s that simple.
и стрельба прекратится Это же просто А
Let’s stop, talk and
давайте остановимся поговорим и
go our separate ways. Before you came,
разойдёмся вы вот до того как вы пришли
we were just jumping here with Glya  you
мы просто тут скакали с Гля ками вы
came and started shooting And you want us to
пришли начали стрельбу И хотите чтобы мы
agree to stop
договорились о остановление
the shooting, we wanted this March 2022, not
стрельбы мы это хотели Март 2022 года не
since the fourteenth year, there has been shooting again,
с четырнадцатого года уже стрельба ещё
but in the fourteenth year, the fourteenth
раз а четырнадцатый год четырнадцатый
year is yours again, look again, we
год - это ваше ещ раз смотри ещё раз мы
were at home, we were jumping with gels Yes
были у себя дома мы скакали с гелями Да
you came started shooting and now
вы пришли начали стрелять и теперь
you say that let’s agree to
говорите что давайте договоримся о том
stop the shooting and not Now we are
чтобы остановить стрельбу и не Теперь мы
talking and you we are telling you all the time you don’t
говорим а вы мы вам говорим всё время не
want to join the bad guys in the company,
хотите к плохим ребятам в компанию
look you started shooting and now you
смотри вы начали стрельбу и теперь нам
are telling us let’s stop the shooting Yeah,
говорите давайте остановим стрельбу Угу
you started the shooting  Turchinov started
стрельбу начали вы ваш турчинов начал
shooting in Donbass once again no no
стрельбу на Донбас ераз ещё раз нет нет
no yes let’s say with your mouth a
нет да давайте так вы своим ртом сказали
very interesting phrase you can say on
очень интересную фразу можете сказать в
what day I know that this is your Girkin
какой день я знаю что вот ваш гиркин
who has now been sent to prison Yes he
которого сейчас посадили в тюрьму Да он
started shooting in Donbass on April 12,
начал стрельбу на Донбассе 12 апреля
2014 if you think  that Turchinov
2014 года если вы считаете что турчинов
started shooting somewhere. Tell me where and
где-то начал стрельбу Скажите где и
when he started shooting. Earlier, by decree, he
когда он начал стрельбу раньше указом
announced that he sent names to catch the
объявил о то послал назваты успеть
protesters in the Donbass, yes, that is,
протестующих в Донбассе ато да то есть
you confirm that on April 12,
Вы подтверждаете что 12 апреля
the terrorists are Russian. This Girkin,
террористы российские Вот этот гиркин
who is sitting with you now, is not a Russian
который у вас сейчас сидит не российские
guy, a volunteer once again  once again,
ребята доброволь ещ раз ещё раз ещё раз
once again, a Russian militant, he was not
ещё раз российский боевик он не
Ukrainian Yes, he was Russian Yes, he
украинский был Да он российский Да
came and captured the city of Slavyansk after
пришёл и захватил город Славянск после
that Turchinov, more precisely, the RNBO is going
этого турчинов точнее рнбо собирается
to make a decision about the start of the ATO
принимает решение о начале ато
correctly according to the float Well, I’ll tell you this,
правильно по поплыву Ну я вам так скажу
Girkin did not represent the armed forces of
гиркин не представлял вооружённые силы
the Russian Federation, let’s do this until
Российской федераци давайте так до до
before Girkin captured Slavyansk, at least there were
того гиркин захватил Славянск хоть одни
some military operations on the territory
какие-то боевые действия на территории
of Donbass,
Донбасса
I can’t say so, so
были я не могу сказать так вот так
specifically, you know, I’ll swim, I can tell
конкретно знаете я поплыву я могу скать
you, but I can say there
бы а я могу сказать не
weren’t any military actions before the
было ни одних боевых действий до
invasion of these Russian morons, but
вторжения российских дебилов этих да
not Here it is  now they even imprisoned Well,
не Вот его теперь даже посадили Ну
yes, I don’t know what you think about a person
что Да я не знаю как вы считаете человек
who comes from another country with
который приезжает из другой страны с
militants and seizes a city in another
боевиками и захватывает город в другой
country. Dear Turchinov, who,
стране Уважаемый ваш турчинов который
being an official representative of the
будучи официальным лицом представителем
state, has sent a howl, such a good
государства нанм хорошей такой добротной
power,
властью послал вой
No no no, not his own, just his own  E
Нет нет нет не своих как раз своих Е
Girkin 50
гиркин 50
people Come on So you yourself just
человек Давайте Так вы только что сами
confirmed that there were no military operations
подтвердили что никаких боевых действий
before the start of the capture of Slavyansk,
до начала захвата Славянска не
you said it well, you can
было это вы сказали хорошо Вы можете
say this since I can confirm
сказали это раз я могу подтвердить то
what I say military actions as an
что я говорю военные действия как
official began your Turchinov
должностное лицо начал ваш турчинов
what day Girkin he didn’t  represented by
какой день гиркин он не представлял
Girkin And Girkin as you say
гиркин И гиркин как вы говорите
terrorist yes On what day when did the
террорист да В какой день когда начали
hostilities begin Turchinov dear I don’t
боевые действия турчинов уважаемый Я не
track events day by day and hour by hour
отслеживаю события по дням и по часам
again by how do you know that he started
ещё раз по откуда вы знаете что он начал
hostilities what how do you know he
боевые действия что откуда вы знаете
announced that Well that’s right Because
объявил о то Ну Правильно Потому что
look  terrorists came and captured the
смотри пришли террористы и захватили
city, glorifying 50 people, so 50 people, and
город славя 50 человек так 50 человек а
then these Motorola Babais
дальше ещё полезли эти Моторолы Бабаи
came in. Well, then there are no locals there Mola
были Ну и дальше ле нет местные там Мола
is not a local Mola is a Russian Well, I don’t know,
не местный Мола россиянин Ну не знаю
this guy Givi is also a
парень этот Гиви тоже
local again, a babay Who was he and
местный ещё раз бабай Кто он был и
others That is, look  you have Dava,
другие То есть смотрите у вас Дава
let's figure it out, look, I was just
давайте разберёмся смотрите Я просто
studying this question You are a Balabol And I was studying
изучал этот вопрос Вы Балабол А я изучал
the question Yes, if yes, perhaps you, yes,
вопрос Да если если да возможно вы да
perhaps you haven’t bothered somewhere in 9 years,
возможно вы за 9 лет где-то не
maybe I’m
удосужились может быть я вот всем
telling all Russians this, tell me,
россиянам всем этим говорю скажите мне
yes, where and when did Turchinov start  military
да где когда турчинов начал боевые
operations against some people there, yes, I
действия против каких-то людей там да я
see and all this chronology is internationally
вижу и все эта хронология всемирно
recognized. Yes, on April 12, 2014,
признанная Да 12 апреля 2014 года
Russian militants like these Yes, with Girkin,
российские боевики вот эти Да с гиркиным
captured the city of Slavyansk and then
захватили город Славянск и дальше начали
other groups began to enter and the
другие группы заходить да и началось
fighting began. Yes, the first dead were
боевые действия Да первые погибшие как
just in the Slavic clash  Yes, it was the
раз столкновении славянски Да это
Ukrainian SBS, they came for
украинские сбш были они приехали на
negotiations, yes, in order to find out
переговоры да Для того чтобы выяснить
what kind of engine they were, yes,
Что за движняк типа да по ним открыли
these shooters opened fire on them, yes, that is, before
огонь вот эти стрелков да то есть до
that, well, after that, the National Security Service met,
этого ну после этого собралась это рнбо
and it decided on an
да и принял решение о
anti-terrorist operation because
антитеррористической операции потому что
terrorists captured Yes the city  Absolutely
террористы захватили Да город Абсолютно
true before this, if you probably do, well,
верно до этого если Вы наверно так ну
only I saw the Ministry of Railways with yellow-bladed flags
только я видел МПС которые с флагами
jumping over the Barricades, what
перескакивая через Баррикады ль какой
day on what day was it, I won’t say on
день в какой день это было я не скажу В
what day, but I will say that these were the
какой день но я скажу что эти были
Azov Battalions And
Батальоны Азов А ещё раз ещё раз
watch this again  it was what you saw, yes
смотрите это было то что вы видели да
it was May 9, yes, that is, already When
это было 9 мая да то есть уже Когда
the war was in full swing, in full swing,
война шла полноценным ходом полным ходом
yes, that is, May 9, yes, the day of the liberation of
да то есть 9 мая да День освобождения
Mariupol from the growing invaders was
Мариуполя от росших захватчиков было да
yes, these bans were knocked out Wait again,
выбили вот этих бан Подождите ещё раз
look again, that is, until
ещё раз ещё раз смотрите то есть до вот
You saw Mariupol, I’m telling you on May 9,
Мариуполь Вы видели я вам говорю 9 мая
and until April 12 again, until Russian
да до 12 апреля ещё раз пока российские
militants started to invade Ukraine and
боевики не начали лезть в Украину и
seize cities, there
захватывать города никаких боевых
were no military operations either in Donetsk or
действий не было ни в Донецке ни в
Lugansk, I publicly declare to you now
Луганске я публично вот сейчас вам
that you have the opportunity
Заявляю да у вас есть возможность
to earn
заработать
1.488  dollars from me If
1.488 долларов от меня Если вы на
during the week you find facts that
протяжении недели найдёте факты что
Ukraine began fighting in the Donbass
боевые действия на Донбассе Украина
before April 12, 1914, you
начала до 12 апреля четырнадцатого года
have a week, look today
у вас есть неделя вот сегодня смотрите
25 Give me 2 minutes, I’ll sign anything
25 Дайте мне 2 минуты я подпишу всё что
for 1,000 bucks, whatever you want
угодно за 1.000 баксов я что хотите 25
July 25, 2000 uh 2T  Yes, you have a
июля 2000 ээ 2Т года да у вас есть
week until next Tuesday Yes, you
неделя до следующего вторника Да вы
can earn
можете заработать
1,488 dollars if during this week
1.488 долларов если за эту неделю
you find the fact that, uh, Ukraine began
найдёте факт да что ээ Украина начала
military operations in the Donbass of some kind, yes,
боевые действия на Донбассе какие-то да
until April 12, 1914, before
до 12 апреля четырнадцатого года до того
Russian militants came and captured the
как российские боевики пришли захватили
city of Slavak. Okay, there you go.  this epithet is
город славак Окей вот этот эпитет
Russian fighting still
российские бое ещ
Riva You have
Рива У вас есть
a week I don’t want a week I don’t want to take it
неделя Я не хочу неделю я брать не хочу
I saw that your Battalions, former
я видел что ваши Батальоны бывшие
football fans, were sent to
футбольные фанаты были посланы на
humble their own Miners their own
смирение своих же Горняков своих же
Miners listen Well, cheap Let’s
Горняков слушайте Ну дёшево Давайте по
bargain
торгуемся
Let’s bargain I’m corrupt but don’t
Давай давайте я продажный но не за
tell me  tell us what kind of
раскажите расскажите какие
shooters there were shooters there were
то есть стрелков был стрелков был
shooters Gornyakov no shooters Slavic
Горняков нет стрелков славянски
by the way department Wait for the storming of the
кстати отделение Подождите штурм
police station Slavi who stormed
отделения милиции слави кто штурмовал
Maro there were no mountains again
Маро был гор ещё раз
Name one field commander
нет Назовите одного полевого командира
who was
который был
Gornyakov Yes who knows who they were
Горняков Да кто его знает кто они были
guys well you said We are against
ребята ну вот вы сказали Мы против
Gornyakov Who  Of these bandits, people in the
Горняков Кто из этих бандитов люди в
Donbass were engaged, it seems they were all there
Донбассе занимались вроде они там все
Miners, miners Which of these field
Горняки шахтёры Кто из этих полевых
commanders was
командиров был
Gorkom I don’t know the field commanders well I
Горком плохо знаю полевых командиров Я
know the occupation of the population in the Donbass, you
знаю занятие населения в Донбассе е вы
said with your mouth It’s not poison, you
сказали своим ртом Это же не яду вы
said that Turchina went there to fight
сказали что Турчина пошл там воевать
against the Miners I’m asking  Which of these
против Горняков Я спрашиваю Кто из этих
Russian terrorists was Gorkom,
российских террористов был Горком
listen, let's remove the Russian
послушайте давайте вы уберёте российских
volunteers from Russia, the Russian
добровольце из России российский
volunteers, the volunteers, this is Russian, these are
те доброволь доброволь это российски это
not Ukrainian Rory pra
не украинские Рори пра
Metz ta Germanskaya And yes, that is,
Мец та Германская А да то есть
it turns out that you admit that the inhabitants of the
получается вы признаёте что жители
Russian Federation came and started a
Российской Федерации пришли и начали
war in Ukraine and began to capture
войну в Украине начали захватывать
cities Well  not only residents of the Russian
города Ну не только жители российской
Federation. You just confirmed with your mouth
федера Вы только что своим ртом
that these are residents of the Russian Federation. You do
подтвердили что это жители российской вы
not deny that these are residents of the Russian
не отрицаете что это жители Российской
Federation. Citizens of the Russian Federation.
Федерации Граждане Российской Федерации
Yes, that is, citizens of some country
Да вот то есть граждане какой-то страны
come to Ukraine and seize
приходят в Украину захватывают тут
cities here, this is
города это
terrorism Yes, terrorism yes, that is, if
терроризм Да терроризм да То есть если
this  terrorism against terrorists,
это терроризм против террористов
anti-terrorist actions are being taken,
делается антитеррористические
yes, that is, the head of state
действия да да то есть глава государства
must declare an anti-terrorist
должен объявить антитеррористическую
operation. Yes, by the forces of
операцию Да силами
the Ministry of Internal Affairs, what forces are these already, look,
МВД какими силами это уже та смотрите
assess the forces of these Terry, listen,
оценивают силы этих Терри послушайте
Aidarov Azov were part of some kind of structure,
Айдаров Азов входили в структуру
this or These are football
какой-то там это или Это футбольные
fans again, who who stopped
болельщики ещё раз кто кто останавливал
the Ministry  defense or
Министерство обороны или
police I don’t know who Well, who who from
милиция Я не знаю кто Ну а кто кто с
planes from helicopters that they shot down
самолётов с вертолётов что они сбивали
another helicopter we are breaking away from with again no
ещ верто мы отрываемся от с с ещ раз нет
again when in Russia terrorists marched on
ещё раз когда в России террористы шли на
Moscow captured Rostov and marched on Moscow
Москву захватили Ростов и шли на Москву
they were stopped by the police with batons or
их останавливало полиция с дубинками или
them  the space forces of the
их останавливают вое космические Силы
Russian
Российской
Federation are stopping the war. Well, I saw two generals
Федерации Ну я видел двух генералов
who came to the Prigo for negotiations in
которые приехали к приго на переговоры в
Rostov, talked about something and it seemed like the
Ростов о чём-то переговорили и вроде всё
military got everything. Yes, yes, and the planes
получило военные Да да да а самолёты
that flew that bombed the
которые летели которые бомбили колонну
Wagner column, well, it’s not clear here, the
вагнеровцев ну здесь непонятно здесь
perpetrators should be punished, not that
виновные должны быть наказаны не это Это
Were these police helicopters or were they
полицейские вертолёты были или это
military helicopters? I don’t know honestly. Well,
военные вертолёты Я не знаю честно Ну
well, how do you have police
как Ну а как вы у вас есть полицейские
helicopters? Well, police helicopters or an
вертолёты Ну полицейские вертолёты или
airplane, an airplane can’t be a
самолёт самолёт не может быть
policeman. It
полицейский Мне
seems to me, yes, it seems, yes, that is, military, that
кажется да кажется да то есть военны то
is, it turns out for you, uh, somehow  And
есть получается у вас ээ как-то причём
without an announcement, even you didn’t
без объявления даже у вас не была
announce an anti-terrorist operation
объявлена антитеррористическая операция
Yes, but Planes Yes, they bombed terrorists, well,
Да но Самолёты Да бомбили по террористам
well, we saw everything. Well, why
было ж Ну вот мы же видели все Ну почему
were there terrorists? Wait, they were
это террористы были Подождите они были
terrorists like terrorists. They shot
террористы как террористы Они они
down equipment, they shot at
сбивали технику они расстреливали
patrols. They were traveling, like,
патрули Они ехали типа
armed to Moscow.  And who were they? Well,
вооружённые на Москву А кто они были Ну
listen, I can’t use some kind of epithet. I do
послушайте я не могу какой-то эпитет Я
n’t know their internal squabbles. A terrorist.
не знаю их внутренних разборок терорист
That’s who. Look. They
Вот кто Смотрите Они вооружённые
captured the city armed. Yes, one captured
захватили город Да один захватили
Voronezh. And they marched in a column to Moscow,
Воронеж Да и шли колонной на Москву
shot down those who resisted, they are not
сбивали тех кто сопротивлялся они не
terrorists. And who is this commercial
террористы А кто это коммерческая
structure? We  they weren’t paid any money
структура Мы же им денег не заплатили е
once again once again it doesn’t matter what
раз ещё раз ещё раз неважно из-за чего
they are doing what they are doing is
они то что они делают это
terrorism I can’t give any epithet to
терроризм я не могу дать какой-то эпитет
this both military personnel What
этому и те и те военнослужащие Какой
form is
формы
Prigogine acceptable Did they take the oath
допустим пригожина Давали ли они присягу
again Look even If  a serviceman
ещё раз Смотри даже Если военнослужащий
cannot be a terrorist while he is at
не может быть террористом пока он на
the front, he is a serviceman, if he takes and
фронте он военнослужащий если он взял и
captures the city of Peaceful City, yes, like,
захватывает город Мирный город да типа
uh, then he is a terrorist. Well, it turns out that Wagner’s
ээ то он террорист Ну получается Вагнера
terrorists are like a terrorist - this is an
террористы как бы террорист - это
action against the civilian population. Well,
действие против населения мирного Ну как
look well. Why didn’t the
хорошо смотрите А что там не страдало
civilian
мирное
population suffer there?  during this, like him
население Вот это во время этого как его
and the truck, yes, yes, well, no one seemed to
и фуру раз да да да ну вроде никого не
have suffered there, the bus, something happened,
страдали там автобус что-то случилось
something, Yes, something happened to the bus,
что-то Да что-то с автобусом случилось
something happened, well, you can close your eyes, yes, that is,
что-то там ну можно закрыть глаза да то
it’s not terrorism, I don’t close it
есть это не терроризм Я не закрываю
eyes Well, it’s reliable to answer you something,
глаза Ну достоверно чтобы что-то вам
I don’t have the information, but I
отвечать я не обладаю информацией но я
would like to return to
хотел бы вернуться к
Slavis, the police were in place at that
славис милиция была на своих местах в то
time, you say, please, look, we are
время вы скажите пожалуста смотрите мы
looking. Here some people captured
смотрим Тут какие-то люди захватили
Rostov, and from this your people are from your
Ростов причём из этой ваши люди из вашей
own country  Yes, and you let them in. Yes, here
же страны Да и вы пустили на них Да тут
in Ukraine people came from Russia, those are
в Украине пришли люди из России те
actually the same people who
фактически те же люди которые
are capturing Rostov, that is, the
захватывают Ростов то есть такие же
same people. Yes, these are some kind of
самые люди Да вот эти какие-то
hyperpathy. SK is small. It’s not like
гиперпатия СК маленький Это не то что
Rostov is a million. But it’s small. Yes, a town
Ростов миллионе А небольшой Да городок
like that.  uh, against them Yes, they
типа да такой вот ээ против них Да
started an anti-terrorist operation and
начали антитеррористическую операцию и
something surprises you. That is, when Putin
вас что-то удивляет То есть когда Путин
Yes gives something that does not surprise. That is, when
Да отдаёт чего не удивляет То есть когда
Putin gives an order without any
Путин отдаёт приказ без всякого
anti-terrorist announcement of an
антитеррористического объявления
anti-terrorist operation, he gives
антитеррористической операции отдаёт
an order to
приказ да о
uh to use troops to
ээ том чтобы задействовали войска чтобы
stop these terrorists, this is
остановить этих террористов это
normal.  yes When is a decree issued in Ukraine?
нормально да Когда в Украине издаётся
Yes, in order to counteract
указ Да чтобы противодействовать
terrorists, you have some kind of zhuzhan in the
террористам это у вас какие-то жужани в
swab, you draw analogies not entirely
швабле вы аналогии проводите не совсем
correctly, but why, what is different?
корректно а а почему чем чем отличается
Explain because the
Объясните потому что подразделение
Wagner unit, I don’t know how it is connected with
Вагнер я не знаю как оно связано с
the Ministry of Defense, did these
Министерством обороны принимали ли Эти
people take the oath?  What
люди присягу Какая
Well, regardless of whether they took
Ну не зависимо от того принимали они или
the oath or not, what they did
не принимали присягу то что они делали
was terrorism, what difference does it make whether
это терроризм какая разница принимали
they were psychologists or not, it’s
они психологи или не принимали
very difficult for me to judge who they are and
э мне очень сложно судить кто они и
what their attitude is. Well, I would
какие отношение у них Ну я бы хотел
still like to return to the Slavic you me  for a
всё-таки к славянску вернуться вы меня
very long time they tortured the paradise department of
очень долго пытали всё-таки рай отдел
the Slavonic who stormed and who defended
славенский кто штурмовал и кто защищал
once again in the Slavic regional department
ещё раз в Славянский райотдел
they stormed the shooters and the company Yes, the capture was
штурмовали стрелков и компания Да захват
radel Yes the radel was brought down after all, the guys
радел Да радел вали всё-таки ребята
who came
которые приехали
to seize the police were sitting there, I
захватывать там сидели милиционеры я это
saw it on April 12 Yes, the whole country
видел 12 апреля Да вот это вся страна
saw this  footage of the seizure of the case in
увидела кадры захвата ра дела в
Slavyansk Slavyansk yes, that’s what I’m
Славянске Славянске да Я же про это и
talking about. That is, the police were at their
говорю То есть милиционеры были на своих
jobs, people arrived without
рабочих местах приехали люди без
absolutely the same as in Rostov, in Rostov there
абсолютно Так же как в Ростове в Ростове
were people in the general staff in their
были в генштабе были люди на своих
places, they probably weren’t shown to us, they
местах наверное были нам не показывали
came up and that’s it  they came up And that’s it,
у подошли и всё подошли И всё да А
why didn’t they resist,
почему они не сопротивлялись
who are the people in the General Staff? Why are they the General Staff
кто люди в генштабе Почему они генштаб
because no one broke into the General Staff?
потому что в генштаб никто не
Everything was blocked,
вламываться блокировался всё блокировали
yes, they went there, that is, they blocked it, and
да типа там ходили то есть блокировали и
again, that is, it turns out that
всё ещё раз то есть получается работу
no one violated the work of the General Staff. Yeah, he
генштаба никто не нарушал Ага не
doesn’t, that is  Wait in Rostov
нарушает то есть Подождите в в Ростове
Yes Wagner didn’t capture
Да Вагнер не захватывал
Rostov No didn’t capture and Wagner didn’t
Ростов Нет не захватывал а Вагнер не
capture the
захватывал
General Staff no didn’t capture blocked yes
генштаб нет не захватывал блокировал да
that is Wait Wagner limited the
то есть Подождите Вагнер ограничил
work of the
работу
General Staff probably Yes probably Yes I don’t know
генштаба вероятно Да вероятно Да не знаю
how much communication they had there Well
насколько со связью там у них было Ну
movement is probable Yes there that is
передвижение вероятно Да там то есть
Wagner  captured the General Staff Yes, completely
Вагнер захватил генштаб Да полностью
took over captured ge completely captured the
взял захватывал ге полностью захватил
General Staff completely paralyzed its work
генштаб полностью парализовал его работу
but did not capture the General Staff Wagner captured
да не захватывал генштаб Вагнер захватил
two airfields Yes from which uh so as not to
два аэродрома Да с которых ээ чтобы не
take off Yes they didn’t work Yes Why did
взлетали Да не работали да Почему эти
all these people not resist But they gave in to
все люди да не сопротивлялись А дали
capture them
чтобы их захватить
Yes that stops Wagner  be Wagner,
Да от этого перестаёт Вагнер быть Вагнер
it’s good since they didn’t resist, it means
хороший раз они не сопротивлялись значит
everything is fine,
всё нормально
yes, they probably received an order.
да вероятно они получили приказ Мне
It seems so to me. That is, for example, before
кажется так то То есть например до
the situation clarified, they were fulfilling
прояснения ситуации они были выполняли
their current police duties,
свои текущие обязанности милиции
look, they were ordinary police officers
смотрите были обыкновенные милиционеры
Yes, with a pistol, and here people
Да с таным оружием пистолетом а тут люди
with a grenade launcher like with machine guns like  with
с гранатомёта типа с пулемётами типа с
machine guns, yes, they appreciated everything Yes, they appreciated their
автоматами всё да они оценили Да свои
strength and did not resist because they
силы и не сопротивлялись потому что не
could not and that’s all And who came to seize the
могли и всё А кто приехал захватывать
land, Russian terrorists
радел российские террористы
com You saw it, you know it You are a
ком Вы это видели вы это зна Вы же
noble man, you hate it like I do,
благородный человек вы как и я
I say I say Zakh Voz Vita
ненавидите я говорю говорю зах воз Вите
the name of the one who  captured the regional department of
фамилию того кто захватывал райотдел
Slaven Yes, I don’t know, I can look
Славен Да я не знаю я могу посмотреть
there Your guys Aidar or Azov were
там Ваши ребята Айдара или Азова там
running over the Barricades jumping there in
бегали через Баррикады прыгали там в
general dude what are you driving What
общем чувак что ты гонишь Какие
Barricades again we are talking about
Баррикады ещё раз мы говорим про 12
April 12 about Slavyansk I don’t know the
апреля про Славянск Я не знаю
twelfth or what April I know
двенадцатого или какого апреля Я знаю
that we went  your national baht which were the
что поехали ваши нац баты которые были
same
такими же
pogrom I don’t know what city this is,
погром Я не знаю какой это город
Slavensk, everything or Mariupol, what’s there I
славенск всё или Мариуполь там что там я
understood the tides Look, we
понял прили Смотри
respect you I apologize for
уважаем Извиняюсь за
Matyuk, he doesn’t know anymore, in short What kind of city is
Матюк он уже не знает короче Какой город
he? Yes, I don’t know, either Slavyansk
типа у него Да я не знаю или Славянск
or Mariupol He seems  says
или Мариуполь Он вроде говорит про
something about Slavis about my damn thing, what’s in his
славис чтото про мою блин что у него в
head anyway, how do they
голове вообще как они с такими мозгами
stupidly live to such an age with such brains, in short,
тупо доживают короче до такого возраста
it’s just some kind of damn game, like yes, but
это просто какой-то блин дичь типа да но
I liked the way we fried him, the way
мне понравилось как мы его поджарили как
he twirled, you know, he has such an ass Well,
он покрутил знаете Очко у него такое Ну
yes  this is prigo this is
да это приго это
terrorism and Krasava but he is stupid just
терроризм а Красава но он тупой просто
stupid rude let's go give a letter to my
тупой жесть идем дали пись на мий
Telegram right now axis vin and
Telegram прямо зараз ось вин а
Popik is even more and more respectful YouTube
Попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
keeping us busy through skarg Orcs in your ban and
заня нас через скарг Орки в твый бан и
even more videos I don’t show people
дуже багато видео не показую людям
at all times I don’t show information about  Streams
вчасно не показуе информация про стримы
for this purpose for Mali operational
тому для того щоб ми Мали оперативный
link to be written directly at the same time and Popik there
звязок пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там
in telegra okrim video shchezh tsikava and
в телегра окрим видео ще теж цикава и
korisna information and we are guilty of you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
trimati postiyny operational link
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independent in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine writing
YouTube Слава Украине пись